[
  {
    "itemName": "hselect_1",
    "roiFront": "200,318,115,273",
    "roiBack": "200,318,115,273",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "hselect_2",
    "roiFront": "570,307,142,285",
    "roiBack": "570,307,142,285",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "hselect_3",
    "roiFront": "934,298,115,306",
    "roiBack": "934,298,115,306",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "friend_1",
    "roiFront": "445,231,160,58",
    "roiBack": "445,231,160,58",
    "description": "日常使用"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "friend_2",
    "roiFront": "716,230,160,56",
    "roiBack": "716,230,160,56",
    "description": "日常使用"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "friend_3",
    "roiFront": "240,310,183,66",
    "roiBack": "240,310,183,66",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "friend_4",
    "roiFront": "504,311,184,62",
    "roiBack": "504,311,184,62",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "friend_5",
    "roiFront": "241,395,178,61",
    "roiBack": "241,395,178,61",
    "description": "日常使用"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "friend_6",
    "roiFront": "508,394,182,62",
    "roiBack": "508,394,182,62",
    "description": "日常使用"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "friend_1_recall",
    "roiFront": "234,228,180,56",
    "roiBack": "234,228,180,56",
    "description": "回归活动使用"
  },{
    "itemName": "friend_2_recall",
    "roiFront": "506,228,178,54",
    "roiBack": "532,226,178,54",
    "description": "回归活动使用"
  }
]